[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":69101,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":89915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":4468,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":94384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":8234,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":102620,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1479,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":104099,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3844,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":107944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1942,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":109887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second o ne to it . If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":15100,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":124987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1075,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":126063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4771,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":130834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1453,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":132287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3572,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":135861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6< /sub> 0  = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1033,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":136894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5515,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":142409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1174,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":143584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br />< br /> (R emember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":148391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1746,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":150138,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5126,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":155265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":19460,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":174725,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4218,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":178944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":4082,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":183027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":188505,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1108,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":189615,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":21081,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":210697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inve rse unde r +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":93955,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":304653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":10065,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":314718,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1050,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":315769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br / ><br />  (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":319377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1061,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":320439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":323598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1236,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":324834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":328075,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under  +<sub>6 </sub>.","rt":1253,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":329328,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":333733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":26568,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":360302,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simp ly be pe rformed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":35508,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":395811,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</su b> 2, bu t there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":33430,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":429241,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":437024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1355,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":438380,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br / > (Remem ber, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2478,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":440859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":6064,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":446924,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub> ? <br /> <br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":11792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":458716,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":4341,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":463057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":469833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1364,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":471197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one pra ctice qu estion with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":34179,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":505377,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":7860,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":513238,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1488,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":514726,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4331,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":519057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6808,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":525865,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":9442,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":535308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":14676,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":549985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":10663,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":560648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":13038,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":573687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0 .12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"The sum of the two numbers is less than 9.","explanation_history":["U","It is less than 9.","I is less than 9."," is less than 9.","T is less than 9.","The is less than 9.","The  is less than 9.","The s is less than 9.","The su is less than 9.","The sum  is less than 9.","The sum o is less than 9.","The sum of is less than 9.","The sum of  is less than 9.","The sum of th is less than 9.","The sum of the is less than 9.","The sum of the t is less than 9.","The sum of the two is less than 9.","The sum of the two  is less than 9.","The sum of the two n is less than 9.","The sum of the two nu is less than 9.","The sum of the two nu m is less than 9.","The sum of the two nu mb is less than 9.","The sum of the two nu m is less than 9.","The sum of the two nu  is less than 9 .","The  sum of the two nu is less than 9.","The sum of the two num is less than 9.","The sum of the two numb is less than 9.","The sum of the two number is less than 9.","The sum of the two numbers is less than 9."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":36325,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":610014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"The sum of the two numbers is greater than 9 so I subtracted 9 from the total.","explanation_history":["The sum of the two numbers is less than 9.","The sum of the two numbers is le","The sum of the two numbers is l","The sum of the two numbers is greater thn ","The sum of the two numbers is greater thn","The sum of the two numbers is greater than 9 so I subtracted 9 from the total."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":30371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":640385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"Because any number added to zero would result in zero whether it was greater or less than 9.","explanation_history":["Becay","Because any number added to zero would result in zero rath","Because any number added to zero would result in zero rat","Because any number added to zero would result in zero ra","Because any number added to zero would result in zero r","Because any number added to zero would result in zero whether it was greater or less than 0.","Because any number added to zero would result in zero whether it was greater or less than 9."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":53930,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":694315,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":8154,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":702469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":6873,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":709342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9","0"],"rt":20162,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":729504,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"This results in zero because it increases the number to 9 which then triggers -9.","explanation_history":["This results in zero because it increases the number to 9 which then triggers -9."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":39380,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":768884,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes it can create any number","explanation_history":["It cannot create 1 a generator  would b e able to create any number.","Yes it can create any number"],"response_history":["No","Yes"],"rt":87097,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":855982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes it can create any number","explanation_history":["Yes it can create any number"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":12794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":868777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes it can create any number","explanation_history":["Yes it can cre ate any  number"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4083,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":872860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes it can create any number","explanation_history":["Yes it can create any number"],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5167,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":878028,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":14760,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":892789,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+x=n where x is = to the inverse of 1.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1no","1n","1+N","1+n=n","1+=n","1+z=n","1+=n","1+x=n","1+x0=n","1+x=n where x is = to the inverse of 1."],"rt":76709,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":969499,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"X+Y=n","explain":true,"explanation":"Y is the inverse which when added to X equals n which results in zero.","explanation_history":["Y is the inver se which  when added to X equals n which results in zero."],"response_history":["Yes it can create any number","x_","x","X+Y=b","X+Y=n"],"rt":50528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1020027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No there is not","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No therei s ","No therei s","No therei ","No therei","No there is not"],"rt":32578,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1052606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":5355,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1057962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":7226,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1065189,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":5751,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1070941,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"It could still create any number","explanation_history":["It could still create any number"],"response_history":["False"],"rt":33582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1104524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":11857,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1116383,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"it can always form any number under x because it will always be able to form any number.","explanation_history":["it can always form any number under x because it will always be able to form tho","it can always form any number under x because it will always be able to form th","it can always form any number under x because it will always be able to form t","it can always form any number under x because it will always be able to form any number."],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":81622,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1198006,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":23895,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1221903,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2744,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1224647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":" 29","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["29"],"rt":4215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1228863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":2910,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1231774,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"College Algebra","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["c","College Algebra"],"rt":26911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1258685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4286,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1262972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - ne ver heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3057,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1266030,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":6160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1272190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"mult i","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3465,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1275656,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1278845,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":3148,"trial_type":"qu estion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1281994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":2598,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1284592,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":2727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1287319,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":2241,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1289561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]